[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What was Harry Potter's full name?",
        "options": ["Harry James Potter", "Harry William Potter", "Harry John Potter", "Harry Lee Potter"],
        "correctAnswer": "Harry James Potter"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question": "Which magical school does Harry Potter attend?",
        "options": ["Ilvermorny", "Beauxbatons Academy of Magic", "Durmstrang Institute", "Hogwarts"],
        "correctAnswer": "Hogwarts"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question": "What was the name of the headmaster of Hogwarts?",
        "options": ["Minerva McGonagall", "Severus Snape", "Albus Dumbledore", "Rubeus Hagrid"],
        "correctAnswer": "Albus Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question": "What is the name of the dark force that feeds on happiness and souls?",
        "options": ["Dementors", "Boggarts", "Acromantulas", "Inferi"],
        "correctAnswer": "Dementors"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question": "Which subject did Severus Snape teach at Hogwarts?",
        "options": ["Transfiguration", "Potions", "Herbology", "Divination"],
        "correctAnswer": "Potions"
    },
    {
        
        "id":6,
        "question": "What was the name of the house-elf who served in the Malfoy household?",
        "options": ["Winky", "Kreacher", "Dobby", "Hokey"],
        "correctAnswer": "Dobby"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question": "Which spell did Harry Potter use to summon his broomstick?",
        "options": ["Expelliarmus", "Alohomora", "Accio", "Expecto Patronum"],
        "correctAnswer": "Accio"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question": "What are the names of the three main characters - Harry, Ron, and...?",
        "options": ["Hermione", "Luna", "Neville", "Draco"],
        "correctAnswer": "Hermione"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question": "What is the name of the main villain in the Harry Potter series?",
        "options": ["Lucius Malfoy", "Severus Snape", "Bellatrix Lestrange", "Voldemort"],
        "correctAnswer": "Voldemort"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question": "What animal appears to Harry Potter from the Patronus spell?",
        "options": ["Dragon", "Unicorn", "Phoenix", "Stag"],
        "correctAnswer": "Stag"
    }
]





